choicestore.com 2019-10-31

# Privacy Policy

This Website is owned by Choice Ltd (hereafter “Company”), a company registered in England and Wales.

We take user privacy seriously and take reasonable efforts to protect it. We have created this Privacy Policy (hereafter “Policy”) in order to share with you our information collection and use practices. AS MORE CLEARLY DEFINED HEREIN, WE WILL NEVER KNOWINGLY SELL OR ASSIGN YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITHOUT YOUR KNOWLEDGE AND/OR APPROVAL. Please read this Policy carefully before sharing any personally identifiable information described below.

By using, registering or placing an order on this website at https://www.choicestore.com, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this policy. Since this is a growing website and because Internet technologies are constantly evolving, this Policy is subject to change at any time and any changes will be posted on this page.

This Policy works hand-in-hand with the Terms and Conditions of Use, found [here](https://www.choicestore.com/gb-en/terms-and-conditions).

We are registered with the Information Commissioner's Office (ICO). Our Registration Number is: 02812899. For more information, visit the ICO website. For the purposes of the Data Protection Act 1998, the Data Controller is Choice Ltd of Spring Gardens Industrial Estate, Romford, Essex, RM7 9LD, (help@choicestore.com).

Data Protection

The Company is fully committed to comply with the requirements of the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR). Regulations apply to anyone processing personal data. It sets out principles which should be followed and it also gives rights to those whose data is being processed. To this end, the Company endorses fully and adheres to the Data Protection Principles listed below. When processing data we will ensure that is: 

  * Processed lawfully, fairly and in a transparent way (‘lawfulness, fairness and transparency’); and
  * Processed no further than the legitimate purposes for which that data was collected (‘purpose limitation’)
  * Accurate and kept up to date (‘accuracy’); and
  * Kept in a form which permits identification of the data subject for no longer than is necessary (‘storage limitation’); and
  * Processed in a manner that ensures security of that personal data (‘integrity and confidentiality’); and
  * Processed by a controller who can demonstrate compliance with the principles (‘accountability’)

What personally identifiable information does the Company collect

When you visit, register or order products or services on https://www.choicestore.com you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself including your name, email address, home or business address and other information. The Company will not collect personally identifiable information from users while they use the web site, unless they voluntarily provide it to us or authorise us to collect such information. Users may provide other information about themselves, in addition to the mandatory personal information (hereafter “Voluntary Information").

How we use the personally identifiable information we collect

The Company may use or disclose personally identifiable information to:  
1\. Operate and manage the Company web site;  
2\. Enable you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so;  
3\. Provide products/services that have been requested by you;  
4\. Respond to other inquires or requests by you.  
5\. Provide you with information about specials, sales or new products or services that the Company will introduce in the future.  
6\. It’s partners and/or vendors in order to fulfil orders from you.   
7\. Allowing personalised advertising on our and other websites by us and our partners where you have consented.

In order to provide the best services, the Company may disclose your name on certain pages at https://www.choicestore.com/. We may also disclose personally identifiable information in the establishment or exercise of legal rights or defences against legal claims, to comply with applicable laws or regulations, to comply with a valid legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order or to investigate suspected fraud or a violation of our Terms and Conditions of Use. We will never sell user information to any 3rd-party not affiliated with the Company, without consent, except in connection with the sale or merger of the Company or the division responsible for such services provided. The Company may also use such Voluntary Information for marketing its products and services to you unless you have ‘opted out’ of receiving such marketing information from us. User may ‘opt out’ by clicking the "unsubscribe" button found on the bottom of the e-mails we send.

The Company may, from time to time, send or post surveys or requests for your feedback in order to help us make our web site and services better. Any responses we receive from users will be used only to evaluate our web site and services and no personally identifiable information from respondents will be shared with any non-employees of Company, except that information provided in the Feedback/Comments areas. The Company may, from time to time, send notices about special offers, promotions or contests. If you sign up to participate in any of these, we will collect your email address. If you are chosen for a promotion or as a winner in a contest, you give the Company permission to use your name, image and other information about you, for marketing purposes. To maintain customer service standards and to assist staff training, we may record and monitor incoming calls.

What non-personally identifiable information does the company collect

The Company collects and tracks certain non-personally identifiable information, including, but not limited to, IP numbers and browser type, access times, domain names, usage habits and other information which does not specifically identify any individual.

How does the company use non-personally identifiable information

The Company may use and disclose non-personally identifiable information for any number of reasons, including but not limited to, working with business partners and improving our web site and services providing a taylor made experience in some cases, at the users discretion.

Does Choice Ltd have a newsletter

The Company regularly sends out a Newsletter via email (hereinafter "Newsletter") to all Users (unless they have ‘opted-out’). In these Newsletters, we may inform you about new features from Choice Ltd and about the upcoming week’s events or special promotions.

User may choose to unsubscribe from the Newsletter at any time by clicking the "unsubscribe" button found on the bottom of the e-mails we send.

Disclosure of your information

The information you provide to us may be accessed by or given to third parties who act for us for the purposes set out in this policy or for other purposes approved by you. Those parties process information, fulfil and deliver orders, process credit card payments and provide support services on our behalf. We may also pass aggregate information on the usage of our website to third parties but this will not include information that can be used to identify you.

Where you have consented when providing us with your details, we may also allow other companies in our group, to contact you occasionally about products and services which may be of interest to you. They may contact you by e-mail. If you change your mind about being contacted by these companies in the future, please let us know at help@choicestore.com.

You agree that we may disclose your identity and contact details to (1) any third party who claims to us that any material posted or uploaded by you to our site constitutes a violation of their intellectual property rights or their rights of privacy, and (2) to other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Finally, if our business enters into a joint venture with or is sold to or merged with another business entity, your information may be disclosed to our new business partners or owners. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk.

Unless required to do so by law, we will not otherwise share, sell or distribute any of the information you provide to us without your consent.

Does the Company use cookies

Cookies are small text files that a website can write to your computer. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. We use cookies to identify you and allow you to log in once to our web site and search or post without having to log in again and again. Cookies are also used by our affiliates or links to identify you as a User of https://www.choicestore.com.

The following is a summary of the types of cookies that are being used on this site, along with information on how you can block them.

Cookie Type| Cookie File Names| Purpose| Active on this site| More Information  
---|---|---|---|---  
Essential Site Cookies | Various | Site cookies are essential to the operation of this website. They are usually set when you first visit the site and deleted when you close your browser. If blocked, this site will not operate correctly | No | n/a  
CMS (Content Management System) | Various | Cookies are set by our CMS/Blog system when you first visit this site. These cookies are not used by Choice Ltd. These cookies are usually deleted when a user closes their browser | Yes | n/a  
Google Analytics | _utma  
_utmb  
_utmc  
_utmz | These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. The information is used to compile reports that let us improve the site. The information is collected in any anonymous form, including the number of visits to this site, how you arrived at the site, and which pages you visted. | Yes | You can opt-out of these cookies by following this link: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>  
Adverts | various | Our advertisers may use cookies to serve you with adverts based on your previous search and web usage. These cookies are not used directly by Choice Ltd. | Yes | You can visit <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices> for more information on how the information is used, and how you can block them.  
Site Cookie Acceptance | cookietab-last-shown-time  
cookietab-consent | These cookies are used to record if a user has accepted the use of cookies on this website | Yes | n/a  
  
Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit www.allaboutcookies.org.  
The Company does not use Cookies to store information such as credit card numbers, telephone numbers, or other information you provide.  
This Privacy Policy only covers the use of Cookies by Choice Ltd. It does not cover the use of Cookies by any other 3rd-party or advertisers.

Is my information private with company merchants and advertisers

The Company web site may contain links to various 3rd-party web sites and the external web sites of our advertisers and/or 3rd-party partners. Each of these web sites may have a privacy policy that differs from that of the Company. This Policy does not cover the privacy policies of other web sites. We urge you to check the privacy policies of each web site that you may visit or interact with. The only Voluntary Information that may be shared between Company and one of our partner web sites is that which pertains to information used in the furtherance of tracking an order and providing you with correct information regarding same.

Order information, including order numbers and amounts, may be available to the Company, affiliate merchants and 3rd-party affiliate program management companies, for accurate tracking purposes. The Company will not release this information to other parties unless you request it.

The Company provides banner and other advertising on its web site, from Google and other third parties, that may place and read cookies on your browser, or use web beacons to collect information in the course of advertisements being served. If you are concerned about your privacy regarding these advertisements, please refer to Google’s (or other third party) privacy policies.

What about data security

We employ security measures to protect, so far as reasonably possible, your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage. We will retain your information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires or permits.

The Company requires that our advertisers and partners ensure the security of the data that users provide to them, however, in the event of a breach of their security measures, you agree that the Company will not be liable for any losses or damages.

The Company limits access to personal information about users to employees, for whom we reasonably believe it is necessary, in order to provide products or services.

May I see the information the Company collects about me

You are entitled to see the personal information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us at help@choicestore.com. We are entitled by law to charge a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you, but we may at our discretion waive this charge.

Can I Opt-out

The Company gives users the option to remove personally identifiable information from our list of active users.  
You may also choose to opt-out of certain communications from the Company, such as our Newsletter.  
If you want to unsubscribe or opt-out of communications from us, click the "unsubscribe" button found at the end of all e-mail newsletters, or alternativly you can send an email to Customer Service at help@choicestore.com. We will respond within 48 hours.  
The Company is not responsible for removing personally identifiable information from the lists of any 3rd-party partner or advertiser who has previously been provided your information in accordance with this Policy.

Where is the web site located

The Company web site is maintained in the United Kingdom. If you are located outside of the U.K., by using the web site, you authorise the import of you information and its use, as specified in this Policy.

What is the minimum age to use this website

Use of https://www.choicestore.com and products/services are intended for persons who are eighteen (18) years or older, or business entities.  
If proof comes to the attention of the Company that an individual user is under the age of eighteen (18) years, and is accessing our services and/or products without the consent, approval or authorisation of their parents or legal guardian, the Company will immediately terminate such account. 

Will there be changes to this Privacy Policy

The Company reserves the right to amend this Policy at any time, in the event that this becomes necessary after initial release, or in the event that it becomes necessary with respect to additional, deleted, modified or amended services provided by Company.

The Company will not personally notify you of any amendments to this Policy. Users are urged to check this Policy frequently in order to determine whether any changes have been made. Users understand and agree that continued use of the Company web site assumes that they have read and accepted this Policy, as it may be amended from time to time.

Where can I access this policy

This Policy is accessible from the Home Page of the Company web site, under the link “Privacy Policy".

Spy ware

The Company never uses or installs spy ware on user computers, nor do we use spy ware to retrieve information from user computers.

Your California Privacy Rights

IF YOU ARE A USER IN CALIFORNIA, USA: The State of California, USA, has passed legislation requiring certain specific disclosures be made available to California residents who use the Internet and provide information that may be used for marketing purposes. That legislation requires any business that discloses a customer's personal information (as defined by the “Act”) to any 3rd-party, for direct marketing purposes, to provide the customer a method for obtaining the names, addresses and certain other specified details of anyone who might have received that personal information. If you are a California resident you may request this information from Company by writing to: 

Choice Ltd,  
Spring Gardens Industrial Estate,   
Romford,  
Essex,  
RM7 9LD,  
Attn: California, USA Privacy Rights.

or by sending an e-mail, with “California, USA Privacy Rights” in the subject line, to help@choicestore.com.

Choice Ltd is not obligated to respond to more than one such request from User per calendar year.

Section Titles 

The section titles used in this Policy are purely for convenience and carry with them no legal or contractual effect..

Payment Partners

The Company accepts the following payment options: All major Visa/Credit and Debit Cards and Paypal. All users are subject to their individual terms of use, privacy policies and other legal requirements, which users can review at the following links: http://www.clickbank.com/legal.html. 

Users are encouraged to review the Terms of Use, Privacy Policy and other legal disclosures of payment partners.

Klarna

In order to be able to offer you Klarna’s payment options, we will need to pass some of your personal information onto Klarna such as contact and order details, in order for Klarna to assess whether you qualify for their payment options and to tailor the payment options for you. General information on Klarna you can find **[here](https://www.klarna.com/uk/)**. Your personal data is handled in accordance with applicable data protection law and in accordance with the information in Klarnas **[privacy statement](https://cdn.klarna.com/1.0/shared/content/legal/terms/0/en_de/privacy)**.

Contact

All comments, queries and requests relating to our use of your information are welcomed and should be addressed to help@choicestore.com.

What is the effective date of this privacy policy

This Privacy Policy was last updated, and became effective, on 22/05/2018.
